<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DemoApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="article_txt_1">The Uruguay international says his team-mate was one of the game\'s best players from the minute he made his first team debut.\n\nBarcelona attacker Luis Suarez feels Lionel Messi was born a great player, whereas Real Madrid star Cristiano Ronaldo has had to work to reach his current level.\n\nMessi and Ronaldo are widely regarded as the two best players of their generation, with the pair winning the Ballon d\'Or seven times between them in as many years.\n\nSuarez feels his Barcelona team-mate is the better of the two, though, because of his consistency from the first minute he made his debut.\n
\n"Messi is a natural. It's in his character," the Uruguay international told Le Buteur.
\n\n"Messi is the best player in the world. He was born with his qualities.\n</string>

    <string name="article_txt_2">"Ronaldo has progressed over the course of the years and has worked very hard to reach his current level.
\n\n"He was not at the same level when he first made his debut, though. That\'s why I think Leo is the better of the two."
\n\nSuarez also had his say on Mario Balotelli's difficulties at Liverpool and defended the Italy international against ongoing criticism.
\n\n"I think Balotelli has already played at some huge clubs and has proven to be a formidable player.
\n\n"It is not easy to do what he did at Manchester City.
\n\n"After a spell in Italy, he moved to England, then returned to Italy and eventually move back to England again. That\'s been very difficult for him, but he remains a great player."
    </string>

    <string name="article_txt_3">
    Rakuten, which made San Francisco its North American headquarters in 2015, was aggressive in its bid to land the deal. Mikitani, who is a billionaire, reached out to the team and showed up in person at the first meeting. The Rakuten name is among the most well-known in Japan, but Mikitani said it has little brand recognition in North America, even though its products are used by many consumers.\n\n\"We want to be a household name like Google and Facebook,\" said Mikitani, whose company brought in $7 billion in revenue in 2016. \"Our partnership in Barcelona has helped us in Spain, and the Warriors will certainly be a pillar of getting us there in United States.\"\n\nThe company is no stranger to naming rights in sports. When Japanese baseball was failing, the company started and supported the Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles. They won a league title in 2013 with Masahiro Tanaka. Rakuten also owns a pro soccer team in Kobe, Japan.\n\n

    </string>
</resources>
